Find the courage, fight together.
Jarhead 2: Field of Fire is a war, action film directed by Don Michael Paul.
Battle-scarred and disillusioned by the war, Corporal Chris Merrimette is put in charge of a unit whose
next mission is to resupply a remote outpost on the edge of Taliban-controlled territory.
While driving through the hostile Helmand province, a Navy SEAL flags down their convoy and enlists the unit on an operation of
international importance: they must help an Afghan woman famous for her defiance of the Taliban escape the country.
Without tanks or air support, Merrimette and his team will need all the courage and firepower they can
muster to fight their way across the war-torn country and shepherd the woman to safety.
Chris Merrimette, played by Josh Kelly.
Danielle 'Danni' Allen, played by Danielle Savre.
Fox, played by Cole Hauser.
Heather, played by Ralitsa Paskaleva.
Kettner, played by Bokeem Woodbine.
Rafael Soto, played by Jesse García.
Jarhead is a 2005 biographical war drama film based on the 2003 memoir of the same name by Anthony Swofford,
chronicling his military service in the United States Marine Corps during the Persian Gulf War.
Directed by Sam Mendes, the film stars Jake Gyllenhaal as Swofford with
Jamie Foxx, Peter Sarsgaard, Lucas Black, and Chris Cooper.
Universal Pictures released the film November 4,
2005 to mixed reviews from critics.
It was a box-office disappointment, grossing $97
million against a $72 million budget.
Named for the military slang among U.S.
Marines, the film spawned a direct-to-video series of three
subsequent films, none of which are related to the original.
The film explores themes of marine corps, taliban, u.s. marine.